《越狱》前情提要K
Previously on Prison Break:
听着，我把钱分你一半 我们就两不相欠好吗？
Listen, why don't I give you half the money and we call it a day?
好吧，六四分帐
All right, 60-40.
你这个偷窃的浑蛋
You thieving son of a bitch.
你最好跪下 祈祷我找不到你
You better get down on your knees and pray to God that I don't find you.
因为要是我找到你，听好了 我会让你死得很难看
Because if I do, mark my words, I'm gonna gut you bow to stern.
-贝里克先生 -什么事？
- Mr. Bellick? - Yeah.
介意再回答我几个问题吗？
Do you mind answering a few more questions?
我们收到柏劳 和他弟弟会合地的线索
We have a lead as to where Burrows will meet with his brother.
他称这个地方叫波修伊布斯
A place he referred to as Bolshoi Booze.
这是数字
They're numbers.
输入卫星导航器，它就会带你到 新墨西哥沙漠的一处
Plug them into your GPs. It'll take you to a spot in the New Mexico desert.
-爸爸 -宝贝，准备走了吗？
- Daddy! - Hey, baby. You ready to go?
开车K
Come on. Go, go, go!
我们现在该怎么办？
What do we do now?
-她告诉你了吗？ -还没
- Has she told you anything? - Not yet.
-那就杀了她 -可是如果她知道真相K
- Then kill her. - Well, if she knows something...
你敢违抗我的话，就死定了
You disobey me, you are done.
杀了她，保罗
Put her in the ground, Paul,
你现在要死了
You're going to die.
你只要告诉我 你父亲给了你什么就够了
And all you had to do was tell me what your father gave you.
你去死吧
Go to hell.
飞机会降落在七里的路标旁
The plane's gonna stop at the seven-mile marker...
日落的时候，在四号公路
...Route Four, at sunset.
-我们得走了 -我带了一个人来，爸？
- We gotta go. - I brought someone. Dad?
我们见过面
We've met before.
-原来是你 -放轻松，儿子
- It was you. - Go easy, son.
离我远一点
Stay away from me.
-怎么回事？ -我认识他
- What the hell's going on? - I know him.
-你怎么可能认识他，不可能的 -我认识他，我认识这个人
- You know him? That's impossible. - I know him. I know this man.
-迈克K -不要再靠近了
- Michael. - Maybe that's far enough.
-这与你无关 -到底怎么回事，爸？
- This doesn't concern you. - What the hell's going on, Dad?
妈去世后K
After Mom died...
你进了少年监狱
...you were in juvie.
我被送到派辛路上的K
They put me with this foster father...
一个寄养父亲家
...down on Pershing Avenue.
他会处罚我
He punished me.
把我关起来
Locked me up.
一个人长时间被关在黑暗中
If you leave someone alone in the dark for that long,,,
眼睛就会开始适应
,,, their eyes start to adjust,
再小的东西 你都会开始看得清楚
You start to see things, no matter how small,,,
因为只要它们存在 就可以帮助你
,,, because if they exist, they can help you,
在你独自在黑暗中时
Help you do the only thing you wanna do,,,
帮你做唯一想做的事
,,, when you're alone in the dark,
逃出去
Get out,
我已经用过各式各样的鱼饵
I've used just about every lure that you can use,
大部份的鱼饵 需要专业知识才能用
Most of them, you need to be an expert to use,
这个电动鱼饵就不同了
This MotoLure's a little different,
任何人钓鱼时都能使用
Everybody, I mean, everybody, can fish with it,
你可以钓到更大的鱼 钓到更多的鱼
catch bigger fish, you're gonna catch more fish,
它甚至可用在大部份顶尖水中鱼饵 都没办法的多水草水域
It even works in weedy areas where most top water lures won't work,
你瞧这个好东西 看起来跟真的小鱼一样
Take a look at this baby, This thing looks like a real minnow,
真的是非常棒的鱼饵
It's one very cool bait,
我从未见过这么棒的鱼饵
I have never seen anything quite like this,
即使过去你曾在电视购物 买过让你失望的鱼饵
Even if you've bought lures off Tv in the past and been disappointed,,,
相信我，我能感同身受K
,,, and believe me, I know how you feel,
-抱歉，我以为你离开了 -没有，我还在
- oh, sorry, man. I thought you'd left. - Hey. No, still here. Here I am.
只是有一些房客抱怨
It's just that a couple guests are complaining...
你的电视太大声了
...about the volume of your TV.
抱歉K我睡着了 一定是不小心按到遥控器
Oh, sorry. I fell asleep. I must've hit the remote.
-我会处理，谢谢，很抱歉 -好K
- I'll take care of it. Thanks. Sorry. Thanks. - That's great.
那可以麻烦你 现在关小声吗，先处理一下？
So could you do that for me now, please, so it's taken care of?
-好 -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thanks.
没问题
Taken care of.
浴室没事吧？
Is everything okay in your bathroom?
什么意思？
Excuse me?
你的浴室传来怪声
In your bathroom. There's a noise coming from it.
是我女儿喜欢在洗澡的时候玩
Yeah, my daughter thinks bath time is playtime.
我发誓会清理干净，抱歉
I will clean it up. Scout's honor. Sorry.
-好，祝你今天愉快 -好
- All right. Have a nice day. - Yeah.
你也是
You too.
-迈克 -迈克
- Michael! - Michael.
-迈克，等等 -是他这样对你的吗？
- Michael, please, wait. - He did this to you?
林克
Lincoln!
是他这样对你的吗？
He did this to you?
Did he do this to you?
迈克
Michael.
你怎么能用自己的双手 对另一个人
How could you do that to another human being...
做出这么惨忍的事？
...with your own hands?
不要怕
It's okay.
你已经安全了
You're safe now.
他不会再伤害你了
He's not gonna hurt you anymore.
来吧
Come on.
跟我来，不要回头看
Come with me and don't look back.
迈克
Michael!
Michael.
不会有事了
It's gonna be all right.
莎拉
Sara!
片名：越狱风云
剧名：断线
六个月
Six months,
我在那地方待了六个月
six months I was in that place.
你到哪去了？
Where were you?
你知道有多久了？
How long did you know?
我已经尽快找到你了 州政府一直让你转移
I found you as soon as I could. The state kept moving you.
之后你又离开了
Then you went away again.
你以为让你受苦我不心痛吗？
You don't think it killed me to leave you like that?
丢下你我不难过吗？
To leave in the first place?
我从一开始就是大麻烦
Since the beginning, I was the problem.
从一开始就是 你们过去受苦都是因为我
Since day one. Your lives are what they are because of me.
对，林克告诉过我“公司”的事
Yes, Linc told me about The Company.
显然你是某种分析师 为了工作抛弃我们
You were some kind of analyst. That's the job you chose over your family.
我以为这么做才是对的 可以保护你们
I thought I was doing the right thing, protecting you.
谁会危害我们，爸？
From what, Dad? From who?
公司树敌无数 我原本受公司器重
The Company had enemies. I was important to The Company.
后来成为目标 透过你们就能轻松逮到我
I became a target. Easiest way to get to me would be to get to you.
当我发现公司的腐败，我马上离开
I left as soon as I realized how corrupt it was.
-他们收买政府K -你可以回到我们身边
- How they were buying the government. - You could've come back.
我没办法
No, I couldn't!
迈克，我背叛公司 让我们都深陷更大的危机
Michael, turning on The Company put me and you at even greater risk.
我不得不远离你们
I had to stay away.
我们是你的儿子
We were your sons.
你仍然是，迈克
And you still are, Michael.
我们可以解决这件事
We can fix this.
我回来就是把这件事解决掉
I came back so that we could fix this.
不可能解决的
This can never be fixed.
有一段录音
There's a tape.
我们所需的证据都在上面
It gives us everything we need.
如果找到，林克就能重获自由
Linc will be set free if we find it.
你一定想不到 他认为东西在谁手上
You're not gonna believe who he thinks has it.
谁？
Who?
莎拉
Sara.
对，身材高瘦 棕色头发和眼睛
Yes, tall, slender, brown hair, brown eyes.
她伤得不轻
She'd be pretty banged up.
目前急诊室病患没有 符合这个特征的人
No one matching that description has been brought into the ER,
我是凯勒曼
Kellerman.
莎拉丹奎迪进展如何？
The report on sara Tancredi?
她死了，我正在处理尸体
She's dead. I'm dealing with the body right now.
-都结束了，你一定松了一口气 -对
- You must be relieved that it's over. - Yeah,
-对，我得挂电话了，比尔 -还有一件事
- Yeah, I gotta go, Bill. - One more thing,
我要确认
confirmation,
在你弃尸前，我需要尸体照片
I need a photo of the body before disposal.
用你的手机照相寄给我K
Take one with your phone and send it to me, and I'll...
比尔，现在不方便，好吗？
Bill, not a good time right now, all right?
保罗，放轻松
Paul, take a breath...
拍下照片
...then take the picture.
我等你
I'm waiting.
（北达科塔州，哈维）
"They traveled into a very dangerous place.
他们来到一个非常危险的地带
阿维德深知危险 但他依旧紧紧抓住龙的疆绳
Now, Arvid knew that, but he held tightly onto the dragon's leash anyway...
这只龙冲进黑暗的森林里
...as the creature ran into the ever-dark forest...
把这男孩拖在身后
...pulling the young boy behind him."
他为什么不放开疆绳？
Why didn't he just let go of the leash?
因为他喜欢这只龙
Well, because he loved the dragon.
当你爱某人的时候 你会不顾一切留住他们
And when you love someone, you'll do anything to hold onto them.
不顾一切保护他们，让他们快乐
Anything to keep them safe and happy.
所以我们才来露营？
Is that why we're camping?
对，这样我们就能在一起
Yep, so we can all be together.
我很快乐
I'm happy.
我也很快乐
You know, I'm happy too.
你拿去看吧
Here you go.
现在都没事了，对吧？
Well, it's all working out, huh?
不要这么说
Don't say that.
你知道吗？此时此刻K
You know, this moment, right here, right now...
一切都值得了
...it's all worth it.
我爱你
I love you.
（堪萨斯州，垂比云）
那是以前的照片
Oh, that's old.
-孩子已经长大了 -抱歉，我只是K
- The kids are bigger now. - Sorry, I was just...
你等了太久所以无聊的发慌了
oh, getting bored out of your wits because you've been waiting so long.
很抱歉让你久等
I'm really sorry about all this.
本地很少发生凶杀案
We don't get a whole bunch of homicides out here...
我们要温习一下怎么办案 请坐
...and we're trying to play catch-up. Please, have a seat.
你朋友的死我很遗憾
I'm real sorry about your friend.
现在的人真变态
It's a sick world out there.
你说得没错
Ain't that the truth.
-你们一起来堪萨斯州？ -没错
- So you guys out here in Kansas together? - Yeah, that's right.
来做什么？
Doing what?
来看看风景
Well, you know, just seeing the sights.
你从芝加哥到堪萨斯州 垂比云来看风景？
You left Chicago to see the sights in Tribune, Kansas?
据我所知，人民有行动自由
Last I checked, a man could go where he wanted.
-贝里克先生 -叫我布拉德
- Mr. Bellick. - Brad.
布拉德
Brad.
布拉德 我不在乎你来这里的目的
I don't really care what you were doing out here.
我们都是执法人员 见到变态就像闻到臭屁一样
We're both in law enforcement. We can each sniff out a perp like a hot fart.
抱歉我口出秽言
Pardon my French.
我们都知道你不是罪犯
And we both know you're not a criminal...
我不在乎你们俩是否 背着妻子偷腥，或是K
...so I don't care if you boys were out here whooping it without your wives...
你们俩有奸情
...or going Brokeback.
什么？
What?
才不是
Hell, no.
我是想说我不在乎你们的目的
My point is, I don't care what you were doing.
我只想知道你们去过哪里 可能碰过了谁
I just need to know where you were doing it and who you might've crossed paths with...
我才能找出 杀死葛瑞先生的凶手
...so I can find out who carved up Mr. Geary.
葛瑞和我得到线索 说福克斯河八人帮之一在此地
Geary and I got a lead that one of the Fox River Eight was in town.
哪一个？
Which one?
-西奥多包威 -那个对青少年做出
- Theodore Bagwell. - The man who did those horrible things...
-恐怖事情的人？ -就是他
...to those teenagers? - That's him.
我们打算抓他去领赏金 可是抓不到他
We're gonna bring him in for the reward money but we couldn't get a handle.
葛瑞和我觉得不可能 便分道扬镖，不过K
Geary and I split up, we figured we didn't have a shot, but...
-不过什么？ -在发生这种事后
- But what? - Well, after what happened...
我觉得葛瑞 也许真的遇到包威了
...I'm starting to think maybe Geary ran into old Bagwell after all.
在垂比云？
Right here in Tribune?
布拉德，你可以回答几个问题
Now, Brad, do you think you could answer some questions...
帮助我们找到 西奥多包威吗？
...that might help us, you know, track down Theodore Bagwell?
我会很感激
I'd be indebted.
我会尽全力帮忙抓到那个浑蛋
I'll do whatever I can to help nail that son of a bitch.
你认为录音在莎拉手上？
You think sara has this tape?
政府是这么想
The government does.
我昨天才碰过她 就算在她手上
I just saw her yesterday. If she does have anything...
她自己也不知道
...she doesn't know.
-她现在人在哪？ -我不知道
- Well, where is she now? - I don't know.
你有办法和她连络吗？
Any way you can get in touch with her?
-我们有买手机，我可以打电话给她 -拜托K老哥
- We bought cell phones. I could call her. - Please, please, please, bro.
到巴拿马后再打给她，拜托
Call her from Panama, please.
剩下不到两小时 我一定要搭上飞机
We got less than two hours. I gotta make the flight.
怎么了？
What?
快跑！
Run. Run!
-你说的车子在哪里？ -在山丘后面
- Where's this car you keep talking about? - It's over the ridge.
把枪给我，你们上车去
Give me that. You guys head for the car.
快点
Go!
快点K
Come on, come on!
动作快K
Come on! Go, go, go!
去接爸！
Pick up Dad!
爸，上车
Dad, get in!
快来，爸！
Come on, Dad!
我们成功了！太好了
We made it! Son of a bitch, we made it!
林克
Linc.
苏克，送我们去医院
Sucre, get us to a hospital.
-这地方怎么可能有K？ -快送我们去医院，拜托
- Out here? Where the hell am I gonna find...? - Just get us to a hospital, please!
别担心，你不会有事的
Don't worry, you're gonna make it.
这是胆汁，子弹射穿我的身体
It's bile. He got me clean through.
你不会有事的，撑着点
You're gonna be okay. Just hold on.
你们两个，听我说
Listen to me, both of you.
对不起
Sorry.
我但愿我从未离开你们
I wish I'd never left.
不要说话，继续呼吸
Don't talk. Just breathe, okay?
好，你想吃花生酱香蕉三明治吗？
Okay. So do you want a P.B. & B?
不想，我的肚子痛
Not really. My tummy hurts.
她的背包在哪里？
Where's her knapsack?
什么？
Her what?
-她的背包，里面有她的药 -我不知道，我抓住她就跑了
- Her knapsack. Her medicine's in it. - I don't know. I just grabbed her and ran.
她需要吃药 两天没吃药会发作
She needs that medicine. She can't go two days without it.
我知道，我是她父亲，好吗？
Okay, I know. I'm her father, all right?
在哪里？
Where is it?
宝贝，冷静点 你要找什么？
Baby, baby. Look, look, calm down. What are you looking for?
告诉我你要什么 我就去买，好吗？
Just tell me what it is and I'll go ahead and get it, okay?
她的处方
Her prescription.
这是备用处方，我留着以防万一
It's a backup. I keep an extra, in case.
好K
Okay, okay.
我只要去找家药房
So all I need to do is find a pharmacy.
不要担心
Don't worry.
看来我们要去兜风了，宝贝
Hey, looks like we're going on a ride, sweet pea.
如果抓到包威 他手上可能还有葛瑞的东西
If we nail Bagwell, he might still have some of Geary's things on him...
像是背包 里面有他的私人物品
...like his backpack, which has his personal stuff in it.
我想他妻子会想收到那些东西
I know his wife would love to have it.
如果抓到包威
If we find Bagwell...
-你可以亲自交给她 -谢谢
...give it to her personally. - Thanks.
你协助办案 这是我起码能做的
It's the least I can do considering how you're helping me out.
不过有些警员有点担心K
Although some of the guys on the force are concerned about...
-他们担心什么？ -没什么
- What are they concerned about? - Oh, nothing.
这样吧 不如告诉我你的所知吧
You know what? Why don't you tell me what you know?
我们找到包威 把葛瑞的物品交给他的家人
We'll track down Bagwell, get Geary's effects to his family.
我会让所有人知道 你是最大功臣
I'll make sure everybody involved knows your help was invaluable.
我会建议让你得到 就算不是所有，也是大部份的赏金
I'll even recommend that you get most of, if not all of that reward money.
那些警员到底 对什么事不放心？
Well, what is it exactly that the guys on the force were concerned about?
有些人认为 你对你的头伤有所隐瞒
Some of them thought you weren't being totally upfront about your injury.
老实说，你没看到打中你额头的人
I mean, to be fair, it does seem a little off that you didn't see the guy...
这件事的确有点奇怪
...who hit you smack-dab on the forehead.
被你猜中了
You got me.
葛瑞和我对于 抓包威的方式有点歧见
Geary and me had a little dust-up over how to go about finding Bagwell.
我们发生肢体冲突，他打我
It got physical and he hit me.
我们常像兄弟一样打架 我不想害他被警察抓
The two of us, we fought like brothers. I didn't wanna rat him out to the cops.
争执后我们就分开
After the fight, we split up.
然后K
And then...
你也知道他最后怎么了
Well, you know what happened to him.
我真希望我们没有打架
I just wish to hell we'd never fought, you know.
也许他现在就不会K
Maybe then, he'd still be...
布拉德，不要责怪自己
Brad, you can't blame yourself.
我们何不把精力专注在 找出杀死你朋友的凶手？
Why don't we refocus our energy on finding the man who killed your friend?
罗伊也会这么希望
That's what Roy would've wanted.
（欢迎莅临哈维）
（药局）
快点，宝贝
Where you at, baby?
保险卡？
Insurance card?
我没有保险
No, I don't have insurance.
你不用保险 要买醋酸地塞米松片？
You're paying for dexamethasone without insurance?
你有健保之类的吗？
You got Medicaid, Medicare or something?
没有，我付现金
Nope. I'll just pay cash.
要125元
It's 125.
（逃犯与家人依然在逃）
不好意思K
Excuse me.
小姐？
Excuse me?
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
抱歉，我没有小额的钞票
I'm sorry I don't have anything smaller.
我得去后面换零钱
I have to go to the back to get change for a hundred.
我马上回来
So I'll be right back.
-那里有医院 -我看到了
- Right there, hospital! - I see it, I see it.
-送我们过去 -不，你们会被抓
- Just get us there. - No, you'll be caught.
那就被抓吧
Then we'll be caught.
我不会让你死的
I'm not gonna let you die.
听我说
Then listen to me.
找到莎拉丹奎迪
You find sara Tancredi.
她可以解决一切
She can end this.
现在就靠你们了
It's up to you now.
我要通报，注意一台深蓝色轿车 车牌AE9268
Yeah, I want an alarm out on a dark blue sedan, license AE 9268.
位置在拉斯克鲁塞斯 东南方40里处
Forty miles southeast of Las Cruces.
立刻去办
Do it now.
真是的
Oh, come on.
干嘛？
What?
什么医院？
What hospital?
他严重枪伤被送来 医生通知我们
Came in with a bad GsW. Docs called us in.
他在里面
He's in here.
我们查过他的名字
We ran his name.
他因为走私毒品 被联邦调查局双重通缉
Came back with two federal drug-smuggling warrants out on him.
听说你想找我谈
Heard you wanted to talk to me.
我有调查局想要的资讯
I got some information the feds want.
是关于迈克斯科菲尔德的
About Michael scofield.
我知道他搭飞机的地点
Like where he's catching a ride.
在哪里？
And where would that be?
不只是地点，还有时间
It's not just the where, but the when.
时间马上就快到了
That when is coming up soon.
可是我要先谈好交换条件
But I wanna cut a deal first.
让我俩谈谈好吗？
Give us a minute?
你有话要说吗？
Anything you wanna say?
一天
One day.
我们只相处了一天
That's all we had.
以前，在最苦的时候
Back then, when things were at their worst...
我曾以为 我再也不会见到天日
...there were days I thought I'd never see the sun again.
但他救了我一命
But he saved my life.
我只希望当初他让我们 成为他生活中的一份子
Just wish he could've let us be a part of his.
对啊
Yeah.
我会告诉他
I'll tell him.
条件如下
Here's the deal.
所有罪名撤销 政府会付医药费
All charges dropped, government picks up medical costs...
直到你的状况可以出境为止
...until you're fit to be deported.
你的资讯要正确 条件才会生效
All contingent upon your information being accurate.
斯科菲尔德在哪里？
Where's scofield?
驱逐出境不行，我要公民权
No deportation. I want citizenship.
公民权？
Citizenship?
算是给我的奖励，我要白纸黑字
A little incentive, and I want it in writing.
我厌倦玩游戏了
Oh, I'm so tired of playing games.
那就开始打文件吧
Well, start typing.
关闭体外心律调节器
No external pacemaker.
这个精采，关闭止痛药点滴
Hey, this is a good one. No morphine drip.
-你在做什么？ -调查局，出去K
- What are you doing? - FBI. Out, out, out.
-你到底想做什么？ -给我一点奖励
- What the hell are you doing? - Giving you a little incentive.
快打开，你这个K
Come on. Come on, you son of a...
什么都没找到？
And they found nothing?
好，谢谢
Okay, thanks.
布拉德，你的直觉很准确
Well, your instincts are great, Brad.
辖区今天的确有派人 到贺兰德家一趟
But the precinct actually sent a unit over to Hollander's house today.
有匿名通报说有人闯入 可是里面没有人
An anonymous caller said they saw an intruder but no one was there.
可恶
Damn it.
如果你知道 包威和贺兰德的事
If you knew about Bagwell and Hollander...
你为何没有自己去瞧瞧？
...why didn't you just head over there yourself?
我们找不到房子
Oh, we couldn't find the house.
真的？她的住址有登记
Really? It's listed.
失陪
Excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
一切都还好吧？
Everything okay?
很好，没事
Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
布拉德，你去过芳勒瑞旅馆吗？ 离这里大约15分钟车程
You ever been to the Fauntleroy Hotel? It's about 15 minutes from here.
-我没听过这地方 -那就奇怪了
- Never heard of it. - Well, that's strange.
因为警方在葛瑞的旅馆房间里 找到这张收据
Because they found this receipt in Geary's hotel room.
是你的信用卡
It's from your credit card.
（铭谢惠顾）
我不知道怎么会这样
I don't know how that got there.
我认为你知情不报
I think you're being evasive.
-请你告诉我真相，贝里克先生 -怎么不叫我布拉德了？
- You should tell me the truth, Mr. Bellick. - What happened to "Brad"?
七年前，我第一次承办凶杀案
About seven years ago, I got my first homicide case.
一名美丽的女子 她被打得很惨
A woman. Pretty. She was brutally attacked.
被她狠心的男友丢下等死
Animal boyfriend left her for dead.
但当时她尚有一口气在
But she was still breathing, barely.
但她把凶手的电话
But she punched into her cell phone...
输入自己的手机 她替我们破了案
...the killer's number, so she solved the crime for us.
布拉德，我们找到收据时 葛瑞手握着它
When we found the receipt, Brad, it was in Geary's hand...
手指着你的名字 他用最后一口气
...his finger pointing to your name. With his last ounce of strength...
-告诉我们凶手是你 -好吧，听着
...he told us you killed him. - Okay, listen.
葛瑞和我 在贺兰德家找到包威
Geary and I found Bagwell in Hollander's house.
我们折磨他，逼他说出 他在犹他州挖出的五百万元
We roughed him up until he told us where he'd hid the 5 million bucks...
藏匿的地点
...we knew he'd dug up in Utah.
找到钱之后，葛瑞背叛我
When we found the money, Geary double-crossed me...
他揍我的头，把钱独吞
...he hit me in the head and took the cash.
葛瑞的死和我无关 你有听到吗？
I had nothing to do with Geary's death. You hear what I'm saying?
我才是受害者，不是那个浑蛋
I'm the victim here, not that son of a bitch.
快点K
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
你在做什么，宝贝？
Where you at, baby?
可以快一点吗？
Hey, could you hurry it up?
时间不早了，我得回家
It's just it's getting really late and I gotta get home.
这里有20、40、50 加20，共70元
And that's 20, 40, 50 and 20 is 70.
加上1、2、3、4、5 共75元
One, two, three, four, five is 75.
借过
Excuse me.
（营业中）
不要开玩笑了
You gotta be kidding me.
女士
Ma'am.
午安，警官
Afternoon, officer.
你有带证件吗？
Do you have any ID with you?
没有，我走路来这里 所以身上没有证件
No, I walked over here, so I didn't carry anything with me.
真的？你从哪里走来？
Did you? Where'd you walk from?
有问题吗，警官？
Is there a problem, officer?
问题是自找的，富兰克林太太
There's only a problem if you make one, Miss Franklin.
告诉我们你丈夫在哪好吗？
You want to tell us where your husband is?
我不知道
I don't know.
请把手放到背后，女士
Place your hands behind your back, please, ma'am.
宝贝，我对不起你
Oh, baby, I'm so sorry.
天啊
Oh, my God.
妈妈在哪里？
Where is Mommy?
妈妈晚点会来找我们，好吗？
Mommy is gonna meet us later, okay?
-什么事？ -照片在哪？
- Yes? - Where's the photo?
比尔，发生技术性失误
Bill, there was a tactical error.
我不想听什么 推卸责任的术语，保罗
I don't want terminology from the Cover Your Ass Handbook, Paul.
-怎么回事？ -发生无法预料的状况
- What happened? - There were unforeseen circumstances.
-我没料到会发生这种事 -莎拉在哪里？
- Things that could not be predicted. - Where's sara?
她跑掉了，对吧？
She's gone, isn't she?
对，她逃走了
Yes. She got away.
不过她不可能K
But there is no way that she...
比尔？
Bill?
我不会让你死的
I'm not gonna let you die.
我爱你
I love you.
你应该知道吧？
You know that, don't you?
太多人了
Too many.
太多人因为 我要你重获自由而死了
Too many people died because I wanted you to be free.
迈克，你当初料想不到
You couldn't have known, Michael.
你事先不可能 知道会有这种下场
You couldn't have known it would've ended up like this.
可是还是发生了
But it did.
他们要他的命
They wanted him.
要他没命
They wanted him in the ground...
现在他们达成目标了
...and they got their wish.
他们会继续追杀我们，迈克
This thing's not gonna end here, Michael.
-我知道 -事态会不断扩大
- I know. - It's gonna keep spreading.
他们的手会沾满更多鲜血
Their hands are gonna get more and more bloody.
重点是鲜血
The question is...
在他们手上 还是我们手上？
...is the blood on their hands or ours?
抱歉，两位
I'm sorry, guys.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
通知边境巡逻队 通知达拉斯的海空军基地
Get back on with border patrol. Call the Navy Reserve Air station in Dallas.
他们有待命的飞机
They've got planes on alert.
拦截一架白色单引擎 A36型小飞机
We need an intercept of a white single-engine A-36 Beech...
正飞往边境
...heading toward the border.
通知墨西哥 取得国际追捕权
Call Mexico. Get clearance for an international pursuit.
告诉他们如果得打下飞机 就动手吧
Tell them if they've gotta take the plane down, just do it.
来吧，各位
Come on, guys.
快点啊，两位
Guys, come on.
来吧，你们两个
Come on, guys.
怎么了？
What?
我们要留下
We're staying.
迈克，这是我们梦寐以求的时刻
Michael, this is what we've been waiting for.
我们以后再见吧
Maybe we'll see you down there somewhere.
我无法说服你，对吧？
I can't talk you out of this one, can I?
我也希望能再见
Oh, I hope so.
保重
Be good.
谢谢你，迈克 这一切都要感谢你
Thank you, Michael. Thank you for everything.
-要照顾他好吗？ -我会的
- You take care of him, all right? - I will.
祝一路平安，老哥
Fly safe, papi.
给他们好看
Give them hell.
-去巴拿马应该不错 -你准备好了吗？
- Panama would've been good. - Are you ready for this?
-我等待多年了 -很高兴你这么说
- Been waiting years. - Good to hear it.
因为今天就是我们 结束逃亡的日子
Because today's the day we stop running.
-下一步要做什么？ -回到车上
- What now? - We go back to the car...
开车到边境小镇 找有手机讯号的地方
...drive to a border town, find a cell phone signal...
打电话给莎拉
...and call sara.
战斗机怎么还没来？
Where the hell are those jets?
-你有听到吗？ -有
- You hear that? - Yeah.
停车
Pull over.
他们要去追苏克
They're going after sucre.
他们会把他击落
They're gonna take him down.
-他们是怎么发现的？ -不知道
- How'd they find out? - I don't know.
迈克
Michael.
告诉我到底怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
如果有办法，你早就逮捕我了
If you could arrest me you would have already.
-我要离开这里 -这由不得你
- I'm out of here. - Not really an option for you.
就凭一张收据？是他放在口袋的 打架？有什么大不了的
What've you got? A receipt? He left it in his pocket. A fight? Big deal.
我在芝加哥的一群朋友可以作证 葛瑞和我打架是家常便饭
I got 10 pals in Chicago who'll tell you Geary and I threw down once a month.
你说得对 光凭这些证据也许不够
You're right. Any of those things on their own, probably not enough.
不过如果加上这证据
But when you add this.
那是什么？
What the hell is that?
你给葛瑞先生的留言
You left a message for Mr. Geary.
你这个偷窃的浑蛋
You thieving son of a bitch,
你最好跪下 向天祈祷让我找不到你
You better get down on your knees and pray to God that I don't find you,
因为如果被我找到，听好了 我会让你死得很难看
Because if I do, mark my words, I'm gonna gut you bow to stern,
还想再听一次吗？
You wanna hear it again?
布拉德，到了这关头
Now, at this juncture, Brad...
如果你认罪，你会轻松许多
...things will go a whole lot easier for you if you admit to the crime.
给我听好 你这个奸诈的小贱人
Now, you listen to me, you manipulative little bitch.
我没有杀罗伊葛瑞 你听懂了吗？
I did not kill Roy Geary! You understand what I'm telling you?
是包威陷害我，手放开
Bagwell set me up! Get your hands off of me!
你以谋杀 罗伊葛瑞的罪名被逮捕
You are under arrest for the murder of Roy William Geary.
你有权保持沉默 你说的一切
You have a right to remain silent. Anything you say...
将成为呈堂证供 你有权聘请律师
...can be used against you. You have the right to a lawyer...
并陪同你接受侦讯 如果你负担不起律师
...and to have him present. If you cannot hire a lawyer...
法院会指派给你
...the court will appoint one for you.
雷诺兹总统办公室
President Reynolds' office,
我是保罗凯勒曼探员
This is Agent Paul Kellerman.
我有事找总统谈，麻烦你
I need to speak with the president right now, please.
很抱歉，本单位 并不熟悉凯勒曼探员
I'm sorry, this administration isn't familiar with an Agent Kellerman,
琼，是我 我现在要找卡洛琳
June, it's me. I need to speak with Caroline now.
如果你不帮我接过去
If you don't put me through...
我会告诉总统是你阻止我
...I'll make certain the president knows that you did not allow me...
提供重要资讯给她，快点
...to provide her with some very important information. Now.
很抱歉，本单位并不熟悉K
I'm sorry, this administration isn't familiar with an Agent...
请在哔声后留言
Please leave a message after the tone,
比尔，不要这么做
Bill, don't do this.
我的人生都奉献给国家 给卡洛琳
I've dedicated my life to this country, To caroline,
我付出了我的一切
Everything I have, I give,
处理掉所有照片、档案
Every photo. Every file. Get rid of it all.
-让他消失 -我是个完美的士兵
- Make him a ghost. - I've been a perfect soldier,
我对你们一直是无所求
I've never asked anything of you ever,
但现在我求你
But I'm asking now,
比尔，不要这么做
Bill, don't do this,
-我没看见他了 -相信我，他一定还跟着我们
- I don't see him. - Trust me, we haven't lost him yet.
林克，停车
Linc, stop the car.
-什么？ -我们得停车
- What? - We gotta stop the car.
那里有座广播塔
That's a radio tower over there.
它一定是接收到某种类比讯号
It must be picking up some kind of analog signal.
我们得靠近一点，回头
We gotta get closer. Turn around.
-你后面的朋友怎么办？ -如果要死K
- What about your friend back there? - Lf we're gonna go down...
也要死得轰轰烈烈
...might as well go down swinging.
好
All right.
加油K
Come on, come on, come on.
（连线中K）
成功了，电话接通了
We are in business. It's going through.
很好
All right.
莎拉，快接电话K
Come on, sara, pick up. Pick up, pick up, pick up.
莎拉
Sara.
哈？
Hello?
迈克？
Hello, Michael?
Michael?
迈克？